听录：脑残大师  字幕：罗兹
新浪微博：@FPS罗兹 @SOSG_脑残大师
OK
好的 观众朋友们
本作发生在Zak攻略冬活E5的第二天
so we got this node again
又到这里来了
Because I know there's going to be WOs here
既然我已经知道了这里会有WO酱登场
难度：乙(xian)
I'm going to go with a diamond formation
我准备用一回轮形阵
我准备用一回鳖形阵
另外本视频不包含ASS字幕以外的其他特技成分
because god knows I wanna dodge the planes
谁叫我实在不想给飞机炸到呢 ┐(´∀｀)┌
not get hit by them
所以说咱要的是回避率
because they will make you suffer
不然的话绝对给炸的不要不要的
（FLAG已立）
ヽ( ´ー)ノ
So, No I will not have my balls
所以呢 这回我不要输出
firmly out and ready for them to stab
牺牲防御力什么的
I will not tear off anything, very violent like that
在这里呢我不打算打得太暴力
Instead I will take the safe approach and keep my pants on
相反呢 我就这么提紧裤腰带 打得保险点
with miles between me and them
躲得远远的
and maybe a crotch plate too
加件铁裤头什么的
Just for that extra comfort
能安安稳稳地过去就可以了
(○口○*)
KONGOOOOOOOU
大 傻 啊
啊━━(ﾟДﾟ;)━━━!!
YOU WERE GREEN
Σ(°Д° 你是绿血的啊 ;°д°) )ﾉ
AND WE'RE IN DIAMOND FORMATION
Σ(°Д° 咱轮形阵的啊 ;°д°) )ﾉ
WHYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY (((((*ﾉДﾉ)
AM I-AHHHHHH EUGENE
难道我
(((;ﾟДﾟ)))
欧根酱
WHAAT
ヽ(ﾟДﾟ; )ﾉ
WHAAAAAT
WHY IS EVERYTHING FALLING APART
这难道是世界末日吗
AAAAAAAAAAAAAHヽ(ﾟДﾟ; )
AM I JUST NOT A GOOD ENOUGH ADMIRAL FOR YOU
难道说我真的是粪提督吗
o  (T o T。) o
Did I just ruin your vacation or something
我上辈子作了什么孽 (　ﾟдﾟ)_ﾉﾉ
Did I just catch you like in a bad time-
我跟你什么仇什么怨 (　ﾟдﾟ)_ﾉﾉ
´ﾟдﾟ｀）W T F
°д°)ﾉ WHAT
OMG
老天爷
(   [主任]☆_☆)〆ヾ
乖乖趴好 要打针了
/aaaaaaaaaaaasaaaa
_(TД Tゝ∠ [Zak])--⊂|=0ヘ(^^ [主任] )
_(TД Tゝ∠ [Zak])-⊂|=0ヘ-(^^ [主任] )
_(TД Tゝ∠ [Zak])⊂|=0ヘ--(^^ [主任] )
ヽ(ﾟДﾟ; ) OMG
EVEN OUR DEAR FUBUKI
≡；°д°)连小主角都不放过 ≡；°д°)
DAMMIT
妈 ━ヽ(ﾟДﾟ)ﾉ━ 蛋
DAAAAAMMMIIIIITT
工エｴェｪ (ﾟДﾟ）ｪェｴエ工工
额啊
(； ･`д･´) /
(； ･`д･´) _
Σ
JESUS CHRIST
、(°Д°；偶滴祖宗；°д°) 、
_(´д｀ゝ∠)_
ヾ(ﾟﾛﾟ*)ﾂ
ヾ(*ﾟﾛﾟ)ﾉ
FIVE REDS
五 发 大 破
YOU WANNA GO NEXT JINTSU
神通妹子你也要一库吗 (`･д´･ ；)
NO YOU CAN'T DO THAT TO BISMARCK
不！你敢动俾斯麦试试 (； ･`д･´)
NO WAY
你敢 ( ﾟДﾟ)∂゛
THANK GOD
谢天谢地
WAIFU'S INTACT
老婆没事 (; # ゜Д゜)
_(TД Tゝ∠）-⊂|=0
Maybe if I just lay here it'll be better
我想 静静
It's not real
怎 庅 岢 褦
This can't be happening
.*.･｡這 .*.･｡卟 .*.媞 眞 .*.･｡の.*.･｡
||\(´Д｀ゝ)-⊂|=0
Diamond formation, everybody
同志们 鳖形阵
DIAMOND! FORMATION
鳖(☆`Д´ﾒ) 形 (`Д´ﾒ) 阵
IT GIVES YOU THE D
吃我Da鳖啦   ヽ(`Д´ﾒ)
D
（#-_-)、
┯━┯
(╯T口 T)╯)AA
（最后Zak他花了五天终于把E-5乙打过去了）
听录：脑残大师 字幕制作：罗兹 新浪微博：@FPS罗兹 @SOSG_脑残大师